http://www.boatbanker.com/privacy-notice/

Skip to main navigationSkip to main contentSkip to footerPrivacy NoticePlease read this Privacy Notice which explains how we collect, share and protect your personal information.WHAT DOES STERLING ASSOCIATES DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?WhyFinancial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.What?The types of personal information we collect, and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:Social Security number and employment informationName and addressCredit history and credit scoresHow?All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Sterling Associates choose to share; and whether you can limit this sharing. Reasons we can share your personal information Does Sterling Associates share? Can you limit this sharing?For our everyday business purposes—such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus YES NOFor our marketing purposes—to offer our products and services to you YES NOFor joint marketing with other financial companies NO We don’t share.For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your transactions and experiences NO
We don’t share.For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness NO
We don’t share.For our affiliates to market to you NO
We don’t share.For nonaffiliates to market to you NO
We don’t share.Who we areWho is providing this notice?Tommark Inc., Doing Business As Sterling AssociatesWhat we doHow does Sterling Associates protect my personal information?To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.How does Sterling Associates collect my personal information?We collect your personal information, for example, when youApply for a loan or provide contact informationProvide your employment or financial informationProvide account informationWe also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.Why can’t I limit all sharing?Federal law gives you the right to limit onlySharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthinessAffiliates from using your information to market to youSharing for nonaffiliates to market to youState laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. Definitions AffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.UniBank for Savings, Inc., UniPayDirect, Inc., UniBank Fiscal Advisory Services, Inc. NonaffiliatesCompanies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.Sterling Associates does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.Joint marketingA formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.Sterling Associates does not have any joint marketing partners. Email UpdatesJoin our Mailing ListWe’ll send you alerts, updates and news about rate updates and financing, directly to your e-mail inbox.Email Address CommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
HomeAbout UsLoansBoat LoansRV LoansMFG Home LoansAirplane LoansOur BlogContact Us Apply NowAddress 49 Church St Whitinsville, MA 01588Phone 800-286-8073Follow Us
Let’s Start a ConversationThis simple form will help us learn more about you and your financing needs. Then we will get to work to find the best rates on your behalf! Select Loan PurposeBoat LoanRv LoanMFG Home LoanAirplane Loan
Apply NowUpload
a Document or Download
The Application
